this is the grand final of the na ti 11
regional qualifiers nouns versus sonics
in no position to do anything yep jump
on straight on top toss them back and
yahweh he's gonna move back but you are
is getting that first one and omni
knight is scanning out those sacks here
should know where he is yes he's going
to show himself but his reinforcements
are coming in quick z3 gonna show the
smoke doubles gonna come in and maybe
the punch man make sure he dies he does
jump off but he might be able to get
safety he's got enough movement here
between him and in husky and he'd even
got it too but the shards are beautiful
from the task and the punch through the
moon he is gone mss sun from sea freak
under control between three he is just
gonna take some punishment that's gonna
wait for his chance to secure that kill
a double kill for nancy quinn isn't
showing on the map has lasso up so oh
that rider doesn't see the gyrocopter we
do actually have some rainfall the
gunner is here but we're gonna try and
pull away and get him on high ground but
no it is quinstock dead stand on up and
if gunner can find him yes he can but
can the snowball connect no he has
shards on the high ground he's gonna
block but a firefight is done so he just
needs to be able to land it just to kill
this kill ghana charging forward has
another snowball two more seconds but
the movement is gonna be there and move
actually fighting through the bottom
line and getting a double kill for
himself while quinn is just fighting
with gunner who's trapping of constantly
husky even coming in to help on out but
his background is just so evasive so
slippery that he's able to almost make
it back to us and potentially turn for
his own kill oh father can't capitalize
quinn's got nothing left in the tank but
i think maybe move on wayne
he is actually gonna get caught pull
back in secret response is gonna be
fierce but not quick enough to get any
kills or save moo and now husky okay
then left him by himself now he's the
one who tp first so he gets left last
mcqueen on a killing spree but it was
gone tower goes to but mid tier one it's
getting fresh and they're bringing
everybody back maybe just jump forward
and find somebody no
they know something's happening bottom
there's no point gonna neglect so you
can't believe back home you have to
really
get quinn to do the work for you
is in this room it's halfway done gunner
is still in town range playing as safe
as possible but twin comes in pulls back
in right back comes out black hole might
be used yep just to make sure he doesn't
pull back in husky so he can't get him
but he does and ghana survives oh man
that's a disaster for snakes they're
just gonna run out but they are losing
all their chances too as quinn as well
has to bail at this point slow everybody
down because he notices the swap and z3
gonna pull back in that bkb would have
been vital right now but you can't beat
spell moon at all from all the damage
output right now from nouns because they
are just running down sq
fada can't jump off anyone he's got no
friends around him as gunner is just
gonna work him in the back they've got
the creep finally there's shards a
little bit off the mark there but you've
got the chuck from the find him and
you've got a triple
dude
nobody's going too far forward
everyone's playing safe and doing what
they need to the only one making real
moves here is queen pushing out these
ways here msf okay your entire smoke got
you two or two down the top and one
kilometer that's not too bad
your tuscans spoke off it they've seen
it they won't probably capitalize onto
it just gonna try and bait out an
illusion maybe get one lasso onto
illusion maybe move has a lot of swords
already popped off is waiting for his
own moment to jump up again the load is
about to run out it goes away the tank
comes in finally goes into but it's the
eclipse into ghana jumping in but
nobody's dead yet but a black hole onto
three they need to burn down the big
heavy is keeping generic after a line
for now but everybody lost mo they've
lost c freak they've lost constable a
and the tbr from husky oh no even the
omni knight can't escape either husky
going down but nobody is taking the leap
needs to think
gyrocopter going uphill
wants them to go on him but enigma's
been found gonna take the point on it
gets punched down a half hp that's got
the old they've got damage enigma's gone
no black hole use barter jumps in to get
instantly stunned as well double start
as the eclipse runs out so you are isn't
doing any damage yeah bkb's making this
eclipse do absolutely nothing but the
right clicks have finally come and you
are hits hard jerk off the insulin tps
out he knows it's gone bad at this point
husky this tp will be successful but mo
the lord assault the don't know the fact
he's a timber thought he'd make it a
while until he died but i don't see him
going out of it neither
do nouns as they lose
two more heroes
smoke action though
who's gonna be seen
firefighter kicks off that rider goes in
punch control instantly oh god quinn's
just straight up dead couldn't even pop
his beak off he had no time no space
he spells off
and he's gone 70 seconds
jumping through
yeah look at him he doesn't care he's
done his job he got what he wanted and
now he's just going to run for it john
block toss away run the other way okay
go and found it cool cool cool
oh part okay finally got pain and bottom
took your tier three let's make sure
they can get away
i think kind of from tusk or over
chances
really
quick pulling back in they found the jar
copter into the black hole just gonna
try and kill them before they can get
anything else done even eclipse shoes
okay jump on the high ground finding
actually deeper he's gonna get purchased
husky just dies straight up and so does
z freak anyway put in the gym on the
deck as they even take the illusion down
with them they changed back
okay
quinn
think target they want they got the
punch they're going to run back gunner
is going to punch off any control you've
got but he will get picked up with
darkness and in zafada
start combination out but he's low to
solve his invasion
both these teams are playing so fast and
so hard right now number one to move
much from back with the hill will come
down and see frick even getting the swap
giving up his own life double sun comes
out gonna be trying to run from this but
i do not think the bench can run as bad
will jump on top although he comes out
but he is just more time for his team to
escape
let's see everybody visually gonna get
caught gonna be running away they can
see the entire team come across because
division renowned catches them two queen
he's gonna burn then get a good position
here but he can't actually get the last
one to anybody ever the duty route on
the looter means you just evacuate z
freak again man to get his own life up
this time not intentionally and he gets
caught right finally swapped on in and
moved by the black hole final gyrocopter
with the eclipse on top they need all
the damage you get but the bkb is doing
so much work right now satanic is there
but it's a double black hole back onto
three they all came in to help him out
but they all go down the same way
sonix an absolutely brutal fight as your
wild the dd rune entering your base is
ready to take it all away
you are
i think this game's done game one
was was a bang 18k gold lead at this
point as ghana gonna get caught gonna
get snowballed into the team and just
stun him up into oblivion and he is
always gone but it doesn't really matter
as the game is gone as game one of the
best of five rational qualifiers go
straight to snakes but they're on the
vision do they know they're on the
vision
that's the question because i don't
think they know they're on the vision
all right what's going to play sound
they're going to actually get the water
out of it partisan is ready to jump on
mss i don't think you want to get
leveled on dive
no you don't you've already put the
points in the birds and the bird goes
down to give the first spot straight to
nouns here mo try and take him out of
father and you are doing that thing
glass back when you are though everyone
getting very low the armor is coming in
but you are is gonna drop first fighter
does get the kill the game for moot is
gone but moo takes the pa with him which
is not the trade they're looking to make
queen needs to dive pretty deep to get
this one actually gonna be tournament ms
beautiful pull in from ghana but he's
got the lasso anyway paul's on back and
we're past he's going to keep the back
rider back instead of the storm spirit
so storm dies
batman gets out anyway
oh no and because he made the tp
mars just almost echoes slammed
into the ground no jump on board z freak
he gets out you get fish comes in gun
goes straight for the master get the
easiest kills first we've got it but
mars is here with arena enhanced fear
then in the versace pinning him to the
wall and he's going to see three just
trying to get the tp out and he's like
yeah okay cool i survived
gonna come back in bishop going straight
for quinn i'm gonna bring the pale but
the fish is a little bit off in here
jump over it and gunner is gonna be a
little bit short but we can get him on
that foot sign and we're gonna pull back
in excellent being used and that rudder
is gone deleted out of this game that's
much better
nothing
because he's gone for lame presence
built not fighting bill oh emma says
burning down this massage pinning him
down just gonna get the egg and try and
pop him he's doing it pretty well but
quinn somehow shows up it's called boots
travel and you can't crack that egg but
they can crack moo husky gone too double
kill for this bat rider
oh give him a chance he's just hit he's
just hit level seven
jump on forward we don't do the arena
for this my friend we've got here
being you toss them back in and he's
gone z freak with a fisher could
you could see it in his eyes like if i
had a blink i could echo slam that but
they're just losing birth they might be
losing a marcy who can just jump away to
safety too this mastery heroes got their
broken
the lord version counters out jump in
there husky is there to save him but the
arena's gonna came back so there's no
spells for you no disruption unless you
call yourself but he's still trapped in
the arena so what does that disruption
even do fisher comes out tries to break
him up husky is gone storm for it tp
dawn in but
nothing can come of this it is just a
slaughter here that's some gold back
into your pockets that's some more space
for you that's a yash kill for the pl
and his tipping point gets a little bit
closer
little fighters
getting ready to go in quinn is back
from the base full hp full mana gunner
not the same thing half mana in his
pocket could zip a little bit of
distance but can't zip too far but they
just want to slow down his push maybe
get an eye out of it but that's a lot of
work to get a tier one tower in the
arcane room okay firefly comes out but
he's being disrupted he needs to be
controlled fisher comes out gonna go to
the chalkboard
careful where he goes smoke is coming in
mars is looking for jump same with the
bat rider here but
they've got smoke on smoke action husky
haven't broken his smoke but ghana goes
in pulling back in the mass keep the
marine away from the egg has been popped
they needed this connection a moment
after looking right the adx left has
been used for the beginning they're
popped around it so it does no damage
moving back trying to get out as he is
actually going to be doing a little bit
damage in the river but you are even
finds him in the back jump and burning
every single thing they've got as the
massage can't get back into action as
quinn is so low and the illusion's doing
their job and now constabilo he's going
to try and get a kill with him but he's
gone out of it so he got the bat but
everyone else does so much damage to to
doing kind of what
sneaks did last game which was
stretching now is going to stretch this
one
bottom on the high ground we'll actually
see everybody toss it back in but it's
that beautiful arena move it's up to all
though but you've got a dd rune around
them so i think you want to do a thing
into the hi-fi going to somebody do not
leave this man hanging because he will
oh man he will cut you down
he just just expired
who's going to be seen shiva's got
picked up by msf bk instantly on the z
pranks we've got instruction to keep him
back for the actuary pops and sunrise is
coming in so secret is gone and
constantly like oh no he's wanted to be
able to be a little bit suffering but
they've just cooked them straight up by
the
insane power they can't do anything
about this spears kills everything
they've got there's nothing left in the
tank for nouns
storm spirit is invis breaking any
smokes you can see
and they can see where quinn is but they
can't see where the pas can't even
masters can't see where father is so to
find anybody they're just going to get
jumps on son comes getting back on get
gonna overshot his zip as he finds
himself mars pops his big heavy and just
puts some shields in front of him so
donna gets scared and runs away mo oh
man he's been left behind a sasky has
already been destroyed and so has mo as
they are just running everyone down
there is nothing they can do it seems
he's going right back because they need
it
just fine
this has an ogre axe that is casually
hanging out roche isn't up yet that's 10
seconds away i think both teams know
what quinn is on the cliff here scanning
out anyone who may be on the lower
ground speaker which we've got the
entire team announced smoke is broken
gonna see him on the high drag queen
goes in just get some lasso straight on
the z3 but the trucks are going to save
masks arena around everyone and husky is
gone but he saves the freak maybe for
the extra slam of the game he gets off
for the vkb he's gonna be popped
instantly around at five jumps in the
egg is gonna be popping up so much to
spray they do lose fire but they're not
losing anybody else because everyone
else has to run got gunners got some
more mana quinn being surrounded by the
illusions it's gone
but move he's getting chipped up by mars
and the phoenix here but you are able to
clean them up three gone two in response
and roche is opened up
[Music]
like what part of values the most
don't
please don't do this because feeling
don't do it please see frank's gone dead
get out of here
that's why you shouldn't have done that
but
maybe take a chance
maybe get a jump in four seconds okay
that range into the arena but the manta
dodge of the spear a beautiful play for
pl but i do not think it saves his life
talked back in killed anyway but that
manta was awesome
oh it's just the abyssal blade here
we're lane
just gonna be dead because who doesn't
want a 300 gold miles jumps in gets the
arena and we've already pulled back and
see things and no echo slams this fight
pa just work the building about the work
move he comes back out of his rock form
and he's gone gunner coming back in to
pull back in mars 27 have the act at
zebra buying back gets a beautiful fish
of the eggs that came back but pl has
been caught again
back to safety no more continue never
falling through yet as pl is actually
looking to fight but he can't find his
angle yet
interesting
i i guess you can't rely on
oh don't worry about it because we're
about to get the smoke
nouns need this smoke to go well they
need to find somebody they need to find
somebody big while quinn isn't actually
there at the fight father is in viz
and can scout out and potentially can
break any smoke that may go for them but
for now nouns are playing it super
saiyan
wins already back
that pinged out mid they know where they
are they've got some fish in firefox bkb
and ready to go on there and emphasis is
flying on through his gun but move he's
being found out again pulled back in and
maybe this time he has some hope because
this team isn't leaving him hanging the
rock is done ghana goes in finds himself
in backline pulling back in but i need
more damage to come for the edge
actually comes off coming his course it
goes down the arena is around him and
just
his shrine to announce team fight here
because it is going bad moves gone same
with pl surrounded by everyone gunner
flying back and getting ready to join
fighting maybe he hasn't zipped in yet
because everybody is dead so two
buybacks earn them nothing cut the wave
and they lose the fight 42 12 a 44k gold
lead between the two teams and this just
might be game two
got catapults one man
they kept this game going for 42 minutes
our cameroon that i know someone's going
to go for and fighter oh okay
and it's on the fingers there but into
the arena could be finding up zebra keys
as we bounce away another one husky is
gonna actually get caught slow them down
but gunner is trying to save his shadow
demon instead he dies no zips away and
dies from the which way gg is gold as
game two going the way of snakes and is
best to find for the ti-11 north
american regional qualifiers if snakes
can take this game out
these guys are going to t.i nouns need
this game to desperately stay back in
this is hiding the truth we're going to
jump forward get onto the spec tops him
back on in and do we have enough control
damage i think we do first blood is
going straight to sunny
yes emma says able to get foot it was it
was too wide if you had like more very
fires maybe you could survive but it's
looking like a double kill at this point
as mss jumps again and sets it up but
they really just want to keep level 6
away from ghana he's so close he's so
close oh just set up into the lsa he's
got no hope
[Music]
would have been handy too but it's been
given straight to the leaner ms has
become it's tv lsa needs more mana for
some more spells but you're just gonna
continue to punish up the atmosphere
speaking of punishment maybe father
deserves a little bit himself he's not
playing too much work being way too
greedy and aggressive on a cm and they
want to give it to move but they're
going to take it on husky
enigma mid lane knows there's a fight
they've got behind him and twin is still
in the river if they want to capitalize
on it but we got a bounty strike onto
ghana more frost shields coming in handy
and said the only way he can sustain in
lane at this point the punishment is
so hard
as they're not done
they're smoking around them they just
want to set the lsa up they just seem to
cross parts to do it you've got to sort
of pistol and he's got revenues back
into the safe place but it's also a bait
that's going to be like it's going to be
found too ever since let's get this done
just jump on top and with the melon
pistol you don't need black hole why not
you've got it so you drop it down and
you drop the specter with it kill on the
photo to position five cm moves gonna be
diving in same insulin keeping
forcing him to go back and quinn is here
with no mana though and actually
chambered creeps that's real awkward
i'll say being baited it's the only
problem he has but he doesn't have 21
charges if he wants to use them all back
in his team stolen freezing field it is
so much bad damage but the lsa instantly
from twins chances at jail straight away
and jump in from msf that wu cox
black hole instantly cancelled and
they're moving back for the brittany
what's the type of glitch and maybe
losing something on the other side but
quinn is gone that's all you care about
as constability is picking up kills but
emesis is cleaning them back up
going straight for timber timbertrone
fan away but ghana is slowed down with
all these glass coming out and seeing
but the chains gonna be keeping this
monkey in place in the middle of the
chatroom and just destroyed as nouns
them got four they got a killing spree
on the timber saw as the father might
just give them the team wipe as he's
slowing this timber down trying to bait
out these chains by getting hit by the
chuck room instead as he's in the lower
ground blasted away and mo picks it up a
team wipe for nouns
round two seems like we're coming in
move is gonna be starting it but we've
got deep on the creeps and we've got a
control coming out of the move right now
maybe we still have somebody
just the same because it kills everybody
but that stolen chain frost no
frost the real jane frost destroys
everyone husky out of nowhere pops his
old and pops away both supports on
snakes
looks like we're diving
control you've got and he's dead for he
can do anything else as kind of goes in
but gunner gets caught and full down and
the midnight pulse just kills him
quinn
just zoning everybody back supports our
goal on the right clicks are insane
because he's got a dd to boot
and now the slow timber saw
just actually died because of it
physical damage be damned your armor
means nothing when the entire team is
breaking you down and straight
into roche out of it so if they jump on
him father's gonna be like hey guys what
up father hanging in this long wind goes
into the river they find it break smoke
around and pull down gunner and pop
everything on to him but husky then he
saves the combo from going out and now
it's just mss that dies
instead but they want to bait out the
leaner say lean up okay shows up top
does this win just walks in invis
doesn't even care centuries are just
surrounding him so i get come on i know
you've got centuries down i just want to
find somebody take it somebody still
spell all right see freak just take us
down to back and dead around it
all right haunted time titty smoke ready
to go but i think
we're in a good position if we want to
take the fight for nouns because they
are all together moo in smoke breaking
position and he finds actually fighting
smoke gonna be breaking picking out they
could see where he is thinking the
being placed down but be very careful
he's got friends
who's still on the lower ground boom to
the higher ground can be seen well
leaner is queen moving in two same
things that's ready to get this timber
still but it is timber he's designed to
tank the woocommerce is way too much to
handle the freeze-filled already been
used to be cappies have been popped by
everyone and z freak what can nouns do
if godzilla freaks they've broken gunner
gunner goes in finds mss and dies same
with husky and constability who was
looking to get a good angle into this
fight can't do a thing they're chasing
they're waiting they're dodging lsas you
are missing his boundless strike
quindo big kill if he can find it he's
me they're going to kick him up put him
down
and lose their hope for staying in this
fight the bkb is about to run out from
ghana but on the high ground they're
really lost three as themselves out the
timber and gun is just trying to walk
away he does get a remnant back but
guess who's waiting it's mss again
as i see where he is they're gonna tip
husky tip gunner and maybe
let him go as you are says no but he's
just gonna work him anyways mss connects
with another beautiful jump on marty and
they take another fantastic fight for
dead one side of nouns a 19k gold lead
and doesn't have the same escape
capacities
as you've seen rubik's
he will be pulling back in this month
king is still rooted in the middle of
the shotgun rubric is going to be able
to pick them up and now but memphis is
there again oh father oh that is
brutal just chill into the bone as he
takes out three
gets double tipped and just destroys the
hope for them to defend this push right
now because there's a dd room cleaner
who wasn't even needed for this
truck jumps in you want comes in emesis
does do but how much can you survive to
pick everything imports and he's gone mu
is out of here no buybacks 50 seconds
the last hope for now to stay in these
qualifiers they need to win this game
to stretch this game get the full best
of five so they can make it to ti 11 but
sonics are giving them no chances here
formerly quincy crew
absolutely decimating in all
three games
it goes way too far forward midnight
pulse comes in they jump in on
themselves and maybe need to back off
nope don't even need it they've got a
marty just pummels the specter to death
yeah three's being pressured refugees
are just going down in the back lines as
they bring in their catapult and now
they're ready to go for the tier three
again dropping the chuck runs amber is
looking to do something side of this is
great hold back the cm for now but you
need to hold back quinn you need to stop
cc and see here as he has taken your
tier three working on the racks moves
going in cm jumping in wukong's to make
sure they have to stay back but they
don't need to take the buildings when
they can take timber again husky moving
forward but bana goes in pops at bkb
again and is just cleaning up
single-handedly
sonic
formerly quincy crew
taking a 3-0
victory against nouns on their way to ti
by winning
this qualifier ti 11 is in their hands
can they do it
as easily as they did this game
please
don't
monster constant nada